(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
hololive English -Promise-
2nd Anniversary Concert: Promise 2 You
アスファルト タイヤを切りつけながら
Asphalt, tires, while cutting into them...
暗闇走り抜ける
Running through the darkness
チープなスリルに身をまかせても
Even if I give myself up to cheap thrills
明日に怯えていたよ
I was afraid of tomorrow
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰かのために生きられるなら
If I can live for someone
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
何も怖くはない
Nothing is scary
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは解けない愛のパズルを抱いて
Holding the puzzle of love that I can't solve alone
Get wild and tough
この街で優しさに甘えていたくはない
I don't want to rely on kindness in this town
Get chance and luck
君だけが守れるものがどこかにあるさ
There is something that only you can protect somewhere
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも傷ついた夢を取り戻すよ
I will take back my wounded dream even by myself
Steppin' out
ありきたりな僕の
Break my
日々を壊してくれ
ordinary days.
異常なほどの刺激を
I was looking forward to
待ち望んでいたながら
an extraordinary stimulus.
ちょっとしたその冒険心は
That little sense of adventure
改札に吸い込まれて
was sucked into the ticket gate.
吐き出され辿り着いた
And spat out, I arrived at
雨降るこの街
this rainy town.
何も感じ得ないまま
I refuse to die
死んで行くのは御免だ
without feeling anything.
終わりの その先も目指して
Aiming beyond the end!
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight 僕らの確かなまま
Run out, Steppin' out tonight, just as we are.
輝く Steppin' out tonight 待ってるんだぜ 明日が
Shining, Steppin' out tonight, tomorrow is waiting.
抗え Steppin' out tonight 僕らは風の中
Resist, Steppin' out tonight, we are in the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight 追い掛けてんだ So there's no looking back
Even so, Steppin' out tonight, I'm chasing it, so there's no looking back.
まだ首を突っ込んで
Still sticking my neck in
見事に散らかしてんだ
and making a brilliant mess.
曖昧で退屈な
Say goodbye to
気持ちとおさらばさ
vague and boring feelings.
関係ないって顔したって
Even if I act like it doesn't matter,
どこかで繋がっていて
we're connected somewhere.
何度だって引き戻すと
Beckoning to pull me back
手招くこの街
again and again, this town.
ビリビリ痺れるような
I want to live the present,
今を生きていたいんだ
like an electric shock.
極限のギリギリで行こうぜ
Let's go to the absolute limit!
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight 僕らの確かなまま
Run out, Steppin' out tonight, just as we are.
輝く Steppin' out tonight 待ってるんだぜ 明日が
Shining, Steppin' out tonight, tomorrow is waiting.
抗え Steppin' out tonight 僕らは風の中
Resist, Steppin' out tonight, we are in the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight 追い掛けてんだ So there's no looking back
Even so, Steppin' out tonight, I'm chasing it, so there's no looking back.
Yeah!
Inside, outside, just want to feel good every day
Inside, outside, I just want to feel good every day
Inside, outside, I just want to feel alive
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight 僕らの確かなまま
Run out, Steppin' out tonight, just as we are.
輝く Steppin' out tonight 待ってるんだぜ 明日が
Shining, Steppin' out tonight, tomorrow is waiting.
抗え Steppin' out tonight 僕らは風の中
Resist, Steppin' out tonight, we are in the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight 追い掛けてんだ So there's no looking back
Even so, Steppin' out tonight, I'm chasing it, so there's no looking back.
[A]ddiction
Don't take your love away, way, haven't done nothing yet, yeah, yeah
Don't take your love away, wake up, wake up, bang!
また成し出した表示は
The displayed status
あなた今忙しいの？
that started again, are you busy now?
未読の毒吐く口もいっぱいで
Full of unread toxic mouths,
せわしない 邪魔をしないで頂戴
it's restless, please don't disturb me.
内生に根くれた可愛げ
A lovely look rooted in introspection.
なんてまだガキね
You're still such a kid
本音は言わない
Never say what you're really thinking
ほら悩ましい
Look, how distressing
甘い言葉かけるよりもずっと愛おしい
Far more lovely than just saying sweet words
堪らなくなるほど
So much it's becoming unbearable
求め手放さないで
Wanting you, never let me go
キスじゃ足りなくて
A kiss just isn't enough
いっそ壊して
Just break me already
Predilection
あなたを手にかけて
Taking you into my hands
Infatuation
呼吸さえ止めて
Stopping even my breath
Dedication
このままディクションしてまだたった一口でおしまい
Keep dicting like this, one more bite and it's over
Predilection
さあ口をつけて
Come on, put your mouth on me
Infatuation
そのまま飲み込んで
Just swallow it down
Dedication
すぐさまディクションしてほらたった一口死ぬほど愛したいだけで
Dict right now, look, just one bite, I just want to love you to death
Don't take your love away
Wake up nothing yet, oh
Wake up, wake up, bang bang
ウー、ハビットオブ愛情が足りない
Ooh, Habit of love isn't enough
あなたには私しかいない
There's only me for you
ウー、ダイジェストオブ愛情が足りない
Ooh, Digest of love isn't enough
私にはあなたしかいない
There's only you for me
なんて嘘でした
Just kidding, that was a lie
この手掴んだ
I grabbed this hand
まだ未練があるのね
You still have regrets, don't you?
あらまただわ
Oh, here we go again
我がまま愛と名付けてまた支配する
Calling it love and ruling again
あなたに溺れてく
I'm drowning in you
息苦しいくらいに
To the point it's suffocating
鎮静させられて
Being sedated
いっそ壊して
Just break me already
Predilection
私を手にかけて
Taking me into your hands
Infatuation
キスで口塞いで
Closing my mouth with a kiss
Dedication
まだまだディクションしてまだたった一向にできあい
Still dicting, still just one bite, drowning in our relationship
Predilection
毒を流し込んで
Pouring in the poison
Infatuation
躊躇いなど捨てて
Throw away your hesitation
Dedication
すぐさまディクションしてほらたった一口これで終わらせないで
Dict right now, look, just one bite, don't let it end like this
Alas, alas
Continued further, evolve more
My love, my love
Is besotted with you
Your love, your love
Continued further, evolve more
My more, my more, yes
I'm a little confused
これはあんたのせい
This is your fault
あんたのせいだよ私は
It's your fault, I am
べたにただ愛されたかっただけだったのよ私が
I just wanted to be loved in a cliché way
いらないそういう言葉は期待するだけ無駄だし
I don't need those words, it's a waste to just expect them
出してしまったシカクがわからないよね
You don't understand the "blind spot" I've put out, do you?
堪らなくなるほど
So much it's becoming unbearable
求め手放さないで
Wanting you, never let me go
キスじゃ足りなくて
A kiss just isn't enough
いっそ壊して
Just break me already
Predilection
あなたを手にかけて
Taking you into my hands
Infatuation
呼吸さえ止めて
Stopping even my breath
Dedication
このままディクションしてまだたった一口でおしまい
Keep dicting like this, one more bite and it's over
Predilection
さあ口をつけて
Come on, put your mouth on me
Infatuation
そのま飲み込んで
Just swallow it down
Dedication
さよなら真っ逆さま吐き出して息が止まるのよ今
Goodbye, plummeting down, spitting it out, my breath stops now
Life Will Change
Lyrics: Benjamin Franklin / Music: 目黒将司
Lyrics: Benjamin Franklin / Music: Shoji Meguro
It's not a game
I'm not a robot AI
Challenging you
I'm not a phantom
I'm in your face and
I'm here to see it through
Right before your eyes
Watch us multiply
Come to claim our rights - it's time
As our power grows
Tryin' to stop the show
Might as well go try
Stop time
So you know that
We're out there
Swatting lies in the making
Life Will Change
Move fast without breaking
Can't hold on or life will change
And our voices ring out, yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
And this time
Another figment of your ailing old mind
I'm just as real as
I'm just as dangerous
As you so know, you'll find
A taste of your own meds
Firing every breath
Fire inside your head
Your heart
And as your people pray
Try so hard to evade
Your empire of old
Of old
And you know we were out there
Swatting flies in the making
Your empire for the taking
Can't hold on or life will change
And our voices ring out there
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
X-encounter
飛べない　ここからじゃ
I can't fly from here.
横顔眺めているだけじゃ　無力そう
Just staring at your profile, I seem so helpless.
嘆いても　この背を誰も押さない
Even if I grieve, no one will push my back.
GOING OUT!
飛び方を忘れていた
Of the birds who forgot how to fly,
鳥達の嘆きのヴォイス
is a voice of lamentation.
凍てつく無機質な世界に　何を望むの？
What do you wish for in this frozen, inorganic world?
そうだけどね
That's true, but...
確実な希望がもう僕の中に
...a certain hope is already within me.
GOING OUT!
何かできるかなんて
Whether I can do something,
もうやってみなきゃわからない
I won't know until I try.
走り出した　始まりは
I've started running; the beginning...
きっと生まれる前から決まっていた
...was surely decided before I was even born.
羽を揺らし　強く地面を蹴って
Shaking my wings, I kick the ground hard.
君の元へ羽ばたこう
I'll fly to where you are.
RAVEN! Fight keep holding on!
何度もループの中で
Time after time, within the loop,
ああ　この場所で　もう止められない
ah, in this place, it can't be stopped anymore.
運命(カルマ)の真下で
Directly beneath fate...
僕にできることが　どんなに僅かでも
...no matter how little I can do.
その身体に背負うもの
What you carry on that body,
その痛みは分け合える日まで
until the day we can share that pain.
飛び立つ今
Taking flight now
X-encounter
無情に振り返る
Ruthlessly looking back
自分の居場所探して
Searching for my own place
後悔になぞらえた
Traced by regrets
もろい生 蝕む夜に見た
In the night eroding a fragile life, I saw it
不器用な風に揺れて
Swaying in an awkward wind
僕らはまだ弱いままで
We are still weak
迷って壊されて
Lost and broken
そうやって続く世界へ
Heading into the world that continues like that
たった一つ見つけたら
If you find just one thing
瞬く星を描き進め
Go forward, painting twinkling stars
闇から覗いた光
The light peeking out from the darkness
手を伸ばして さあ行こう
Reach out your hand, let's go
走り出したこの思い
These feelings that have started running
ほら心の星が導いて
Look, the star of the heart is leading the way
染み付いてる癒えない傷を
Taking these stained, unhealable wounds
この翼で運び出す X-encounter
With these wings, X-encounter
I'll keep holding on 空を切り
I'll keep holding on, cutting through the sky
形のない涙も蹴散らして
Scattering even the formless tears
凛とした目に宿る灯火を
The light dwelling in your dignified eyes
曇らせはしない 君はそのままいて
I won't let it cloud over, just stay as you are
向かい風に逆らい
Against the headwind
小さな羽 広げ目指そう
Let's spread our small wings and aim
僕ら果てる日まで
Until the day we expire
ともに駆けてゆこう X-encounter
Let's run together, X-encounter
誰のせいでもない涙
Tears that aren't anyone's fault
誇りにして さあ行こう
Take pride in them, let's go
走り出す始まりへ
To the beginning where we start running
きっと生まれる前から決まっていた
It was surely decided before we were born
羽を揺らし強く地を蹴って
Swaying wings and kicking the ground hard
君の元へ 羽ばたく X-encounter
Taking flight to your side, X-encounter
I'll keep holding on
何千の後悔の後に響く鼓動
A heartbeat echoing after thousands of regrets
この一瞬が永遠へ変わる
This moment changes into eternity
手を繋ぎ刺して 世界を見に行こう
Let's hold hands and go see the world
皮肉にも僕たちは
Ironically, we
嘆きよりくぐり抜けて知るんだろう
Will know it by passing through more than grieving
生存の意味を
The meaning of existence
真実へと駆けてゆこう
Let's run towards the truth
遠回りそれは幸福との
The detour, that's with happiness
景色にも愛を持てた時に
When we can have love for the scenery too
世界はまた
The world will
生まれ変わる
Be reborn once again
Thank you so much for watching the anniversary!
So far!
Are you guys having a good time?
Don't forget to share your comments
using the hashtag shown at the top right of the screen!
#Promise2U!
Alright, we're currently at the Promise Hideout!
Over there!
Oh my god, that is huge!
Oh my god, it's so pretty!
Whoa! I was way too excited!
Don't die! Don't die!
Now that we also have such a fancy stage
on the rooftop as well and everything,
let's turn things up with some fun variety games!
I bet you guys are probably feeling a bit tired
after that intense first half of this live, right?
I'm good! I'm alive, upstanding!
To help you recover from that fatigue and tiredness,
I've prepared the perfect segment for you guys!
Pleasure or Pain? Promise Foot Massage Karaoke Battle!
Pleasure or Pain? Promise Foot Massage Karaoke Battle
Each member will sing one chorus from two songs they're good at!
Battle it out by total score using the scoring system.
Foot pressure point massage while singing...
Can they hold out and finish the song?
Place 2nd or lower and drink the super sour geki-suppa juice as punishment!
Ta-da! It's a foot reflexology mat!
First Half: Foot Reflexology Mat
So, who's brave enough to go first?
Fine, I'll go first!
I am going to sing "Zankyou Sanka"!
Aah! Ooh!
Oh! Ouch! She's fine!
Aah! Oh my god! Keep walking!
Aah! Ouch! It hurts!
誰が袖に咲く幻花
Who is the phantom flower blooming on their sleeve?
ただそこに藍を落とした
Just dropping indigo there.
派手に色を溶かす夜に
In a night that flamboyantly dissolves colors.
銀朱の月を添えて
Accompanied by a vermillion moon.
転がるように風を切って
Cutting through the wind as if rolling.
躓くごとに強くなった
Strengthened by every stumble.
光も痛みも怒りも全部
Embracing all the light, pain, and anger.
抱きしめて
Embrace it all!
選ばれなければ　選べばいい
If you aren't chosen, then just choose for yourself.
声よ轟け　夜のその向こうへ
Let your voice roar, to the other side of the night.
涙で滲んでた
Blurred by tears,
あんなに遠くの景色まで
even that distant landscape.
響き渡れ
Resonate far and wide.
何を奏でて？　誰に届けたくて？
What are you playing? Who do you want to reach?
不確かなままでいい
It's okay to be uncertain.
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the feelings,
どんなに長い葛藤も
no matter how long the conflict,
歌と散れ　残響
scatter with the song, reverberation!
Ow! Okay.
I can barely balance.
You need grip, kid.
Oh, there you go.
Oh my god, that hurt.
How's your blood flow? Do you feel...
How do you... do you feel refreshed?
You look great.
Alright! Looks like the score is in.
Shall we see the score?
Hi! This is what you got! Ta-da!
70.161 pts.
I've never... I've never gotten
a score that low before.
70.161! That's so good! That's good!
That's good, what are you talking about?
You know, 70, that's a...
That's a... that's a C, no, B. That's a B.
That's a... B-minus? B-minus.
Yeah, that's good. Isn't it a B-minus?
That's a C, that's a C-minus.
No... no... it's a B-minus.
Alrighty then. Who wants to go next?
Senpai! Senpai!
Senpai ja nai... we're from...
We're not senpai... we're from...
We're from the same... She's senpai by two hours.
Was it two hours?
Yeah, I think it was around two hours.
You guys are very...
I've never heard that from you before.
Okay, I guess... yeah!
Oh go.
Here you go! Gonna have so much fun!
Okay, so Kronii, what song are you going to sing for us?
Um, I'm going to be singing "Mousou Zei".
Woah! Super "Mousou Zei".
Um, I'm going to be singing "Delusion Tax".
Woah! Super "Delusion Tax".
Yay! 'Cause I only know old songs.
Yay! That's great!
I know that song!
Okay then. All right, please start the music.
Music start-o!
Uh oh, okay. She sounds so confused.
You're gonna be fine.
You're gonna be fine. You're on
the edge of the mat by the way.
あの娘もいいな　あの娘もいいな
That girl is nice, and that girl too
頭の中でイイコトしてる
Doing good things in my head
あなたはそれで満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは思いませんか？
Don't you want to make it come true?
You're on a good spot right now. You're doing good.
あの子でいいや　あのこでいいや
That girl is fine, that girl is fine
妥協大好き飲む針千本
Love compromise, swallow a thousand needles
あなたはそれで満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは思いませんか？
Don't you want to make it come true?
納めましょう妄想税
Let's pay the delusion tax
皆様の暮らしを豊かにするために
To make everyone's lives richer
叶えたい　たい　たいを現実に
Making your wants, wants, wants a reality
今　未来来来来を買い戻せ
Now, buy back the future, ture, ture, ture
アレしたいしたい病も欲しがりも
The "want to do that" disease and the greediness
さあ、痛いいたいいたい　その向こうへ
Come on, beyond the pain, pain, pain
そう、汚い妄想は汚いお金で解決させましょう
Yes, let's solve dirty delusions with dirty money
Yeah! Yeah!
Woah! You did amazing! Wow!
I feel like that brought out like a...
like a roughness. Woah!
Could actually sing on that? Oh wow.
Blood circulation... that's a lot of blood circulation.
Oh my god. Wow.
Alright, the score is in. Let's see what Kronii got.
73.864 pts.
Woah! Yay!
73! Oh my god!
Wait wait, it's still first half.
I can still make it. Mada zenhan.
I can still make it. It's still the first half.
Alright, I'll go! My turn!
I'm excited. I've been wanting to
sing this song for so long.
Okay, what song is it? What are you singing?
A-RI-TA-KE! Yakusoku no Hi! Finally,
I finally found an instrumental track.
Everything I have! The Promised Day! Finally,
I'm so excited.
Your childhood, I'm assuming. Shout... not really.
Not really. Nice, Fairy Tail.
Now, okay.
Now that you're ready, please hop onto
the foot reflexology mat. Come on.
Yes. You ready? You ready? Yeah. Okay.
Now please start singing. Music start-o! Yay!
フェアリーテイル
Fairy Tail
この手で掴んだ光は
The light I grabbed with these hands
Woah! You're walking! You're walking!
夢に描いた理想郷
The utopia I drew in my dreams
You're great! Yeah! Let's go!
夢のまま終わらせない
I won't let it end as just a dream
いつか会える
Someday I'll meet
未来の僕に伝えたい
The future me I want to tell
時に未来は残酷で
Sometimes the future is cruel
鏡のように割れるけど
And breaks like a mirror
欠片を失くさないよう
So as not to lose the pieces
見つけ出せばいい
I just have to find them
凍える闇が
The freezing darkness
僕たちの行く手塞いでも
Even if it blocks our path
きっと忘れない　希望
Surely I won't forget the hope
フェアリーテイル
Fairy Tail
この手で掴んだ光は
The light I grabbed with these hands
絆の力　溢れているから
Because the power of bonds is overflowing
絆の力 溢れているから
Because the power of our bond is overflowing
だから譲れない 揺るがない
So I won't give in, I won't waver
僕らは知っている 悲しい涙を
We know those sad tears
だから譲れない 揺るがない
So I won't give in, I won't waver
夢見た あの日に そう 辿り着くまで
Until I reach that day I dreamed of
Yeah! Whoo!
Yo, you guys can sing on this thing!
How was it?
It brings out something... in... from deep within!
From within? Okay then!
Since you have something deep within, it's time to see what score that brought you! Hah!
1st Challenge: 81.434 pts.
Whoa, she got an 81.434! Whoa!
Currently in the first place is Hakos Baelz with a 81.434 points.
Any comments heading into the second half now?
I'm excited!
I'll continue to do my best so that I don't have to do the juice...
...content!
頑張るぞ！
I'll do my best!
Alrighty then, let me introduce the next key item, or should I say person for the second half...
...in this foot massage battle, yeah?
では、お入りください。どうぞ！
Now, please come in. This way!
Second Half Foot Massage Therapist
こんにちは。
Hello.
こんにちは！
Hello!
Okay, let me introduce you guys to Takita-san,
who will be giving us foot massages, a foot massage pro!
Foot Massage Therapist: Naoko Takita (瀧田奈緒子)
Foot Massage Therapist: Naoko Takita (Naoko Takita)
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
ああ、怖い。
Ah, scary.
怖いね。
Scary, isn't it.
So scary.
痛いですか？
Is it painful?
痛いです。
It's painful.
Alright, okay, since it's gonna hurt, who wants to kick things off?
Alright, since I went last last time, I'll go first this time!
What are you going to sing?
Um... I'm going to be singing "Baka Mitai"!
行きます！
Here I go!
Okay then, please get ready! Takita-san mo yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Okay then, please get ready! Takita-san, please also take care of her!
優しくしてください...
Please be gentle...
怖い！
Scary!
大丈夫、健康にいいんだから。 It's good for your health!
It's okay, it's good for your health. It's good for your health!
Let's go!
Okay then, please start the music! Start!
Inner peace... Inner peace...
馬鹿みたい 子供なのね
I'm a fool, just like a child
夢を追って傷ついて
Chasing dreams and getting hurt
You're doing great! Yeah!
嘘が下手なくせに
Despite being a bad liar
笑えない 笑顔見せた
You showed me a smile that couldn't laugh
I love you!
I love you も ろくに言わない
I can't even say "I love you" properly
口下手で ほんまに 不器用
Poor with words and truly clumsy
なーのになのにどうして
And yet, and yet, why
サヨナラは言えたの
Were you able to say goodbye?
You were able to say goodbye
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, it's no good, it's just no good
あんたが 好きで好きすぎて
I love you, I love you way too much
どれだけ 強いお酒でも 歪まない思い出が 馬鹿みたい
No matter how strong the drink, the memories won't blur, I'm such a fool
歪まない 思い出が 馬鹿みたい
The memories won't blur, I'm such a fool
先生、先生、ありがとうございます！おお、ありがとうございます！
Sensei, sensei, thank you! Oh, thank you!
Oh, that was a beautiful ending to that song.
That's scary, oh my god.
Alrighty, how was that? How was the song while getting a foot massage, yeah?
I can't feel my big toe.
Now the score is in. Let's see what you got! Jajang!
2nd Challenge: 68.057 pts.
You got a 68.057!
Hey hey hey, it's over 50. So close to a good number, yeah.
痛！痛！ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
It hurts! It hurts! Thank you! Thank you!
健康になった、 you became a bit healthy.
You became healthy, you became a bit healthy.
健康に、健康になりました。
Healthy, I've become healthy.
A lot healthy. Yeah.
She's... it's really that bad? Oh my god.
You're not exaggerating, are you?
大げさじゃない！
I'm not exaggerating!
やってよもう！
Do it already, seriously!
I want, I want to try.
Okay, Kronii's up! Before you sit, what are you going to sing?
Alright, oh yeah!
I'm gonna sing "Usseewa".
Alrighty, please get ready.
滝田様、またよろしくお願いします。
Mr. Takita, thank you for your help again.
お願いします！
We're counting on you!
ガチ痛い、ガチ痛い！
It really hurts, it really hurts!
You're gonna... you're done, you're done.
You don't have to worry.
Yay! Okay then, let's go!
Music, start!
I don't think it's gonna be that bad.
思い切りやっちゃって！
Go all out!
正しさとは　愚かさとは
What is rightness? What is foolishness?
それが何か見せつけてやる
I'll show you exactly what it is.
Oh, she's fine! Yes, she's fine!
She's slowly warms up.
Oh! Oh wow!
ちっちゃな頃から優等生
I've been a model student since I was small,
気づいたら大人になっていた
And before I knew it, I was an adult.
ナイフの様な思考回路
A thought process like a knife,
持ち合わせる訳もなく
Is something I've never had.
でも遊び足りない　何か足りない
But I haven't played enough, something is missing.
困っちまうこれは誰かのせい
It's troubling, and it's someone's fault.
あてもなくただ混乱するエイディー
Just aimlessly confused, A-D-Y.
それもそっか
Well, that's that.
最新の流行は当然の把握
Keeping up with the latest trends is a given.
経済の動向も通勤時チェック
Checking economic trends during the commute,
純情な精神で入社しワーク
Joining a company and working with a pure spirit,
社会人じゃ当然のルールです
These are the obvious rules of society.
はぁ？
Huh?
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
あなたが思うより健康です
I'm healthier than you think.
一切合切凡庸な
Everything and anything is mediocre,
あなたじゃ分からないかもね
So you probably wouldn't understand.
嗚呼よく似合う
その可もなく不可もないメロディー
Ah, it suits you well,
that melody that's neither good nor bad.
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
頭の出来が違うので問題はナシ
The way our heads are built is different,
so there's no problem.
すごーい！ わあ！ イェーイ！
Incredible! Wow! Yay!
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
It sounded like you were in a massage.
イェーイ！ マッサージされてる。
I feel so good! Yay!
Yay! I'm getting a massage.
え？ マジ？
Eh? Really?
Alrighty then, the score's in again.
Let's see what you got.
結果をお願いします！ ジャジャン！
Let's see the results! Ta-da!
Yay! Woooo!
She got a 77.994,
that's literally a 78! That's so good!
Alright, well, who's left?
Who's left?
We only have one person left!
IRyS-chama!
はい、はい。
Yes, yes.
行きなさい、早く。 はい。
Go on, quickly. Yes.
Let's go, let's go!
What song are you singing?
I am going to be singing "Akuma no Ko"
because the world is just that cruel.
世界は残酷です。
The world is cruel.
先生も本当に思い切りやってください。
Teacher, please really go all out on her.
怖い... はい。
Scary... yes.
優しくしてください！
Please be gentle!
強くて！ 強くて！
Strong! Strong!
Alright, you ready?
I'm scared.
Yes! じゃあ、ミュージック・スタート！
Woooo!
Yes! Okay, music start!
Oh, my heart's beating.
鉄の弾が正義の証明
Iron bullets are the proof of justice.
貫けば英雄に近づいた
If they pierce through, they bring us closer
to becoming heroes.
その目を閉じて触れてみれば
If you close those eyes and try to touch it,
同じ形　同じ体温の悪魔
It's a devil with the same shape
and the same body temperature.
僕はダメで　あいつはいいの？
I'm no good, but he's fine?
そこに壁があっただけなのに
Even though there was just a wall there.
生まれてしまった運命嘆くな
Don't lament the fate of being born.
僕らはみんな自由なんだから
Because we are all free.
鳥のように羽があれば
If I had wings like a bird,
どこへだって行けるけど
I could go anywhere.
帰る場所がなければ
If there's no place to return to,
きっとどこへも行けない
I'm sure I won't be able to go anywhere.
ただただ生きるのは嫌だ
I hate just simply living.
世界は残酷だ
The world is cruel,
それでも君を愛すよ
But I'll still love you.
なにを犠牲にしても
No matter what I have to sacrifice,
それでも君を守るよ
I'll still protect you.
間違いだとしても
Even if it's a mistake,
疑ったりしない
I won't doubt it.
正しさとは自分のこと
Rightness is about yourself,
強く信じることだ
It's about believing strongly.
Aaaaaah...
だろ！ How was it?
How do you feel?
Right! How was it?
Was it refreshing?
Refreshing, right?
That was great!
素晴らしい体験をさせていただきました。 痛っ...
I was given a wonderful experience. Ouch...
Alright, I feel like the scores are in.
Shall we see?
ジャジャン！
Ta-da!
Oh! Ohhh! You did so good!
77.716!
Wooo! Yay!
And that concludes the second half.
My big toe still hurts so bad!
I know. みんな痛がってます。
滝田さん、ありがとうございました。
I know. Everyone is in pain.
Mr. Takita, thank you very much.
ありがとうございました！
痛気持ちよかったです。 バイバイ！
Thank you very much!
It was a good kind of pain. Bye bye!
Okay then!
I present to you the final scores! Tadah! Tadah!
Total Score
The one and only first place
with 151,858 points is... Ouro Kronii!
Champion Ouro Kronii
Yay! Whoo!
The healthiest of us all!
How do you feel? How do you feel? How do you feel?
Oh, I wish I got a massage
for my left side too, that would have been so nice.
But you know, I'm so happy that we got to suffer together!
Yay! Yay!
Okay, now with that wholesome moment aside...
Yeah, let's get back to the live—
Not yet! Not yet! Not yet! No!
Actually, yeah, let's get back to the live! No! No!
We should get back to the live! Yeah, I think it's time!
It's time for the punishment game!
Staff-san, please prepare! Thank you, thank you!
Okay, so they said it was like a super sour drink.
Yeah, I heard it's a sour drink.
Why is it—? It smells— It smells healthy.
Oh wait, it smells good though.
It smells like ass.
Mmm... It's like... Ume? Maybe? Is it Ume? It smells Ume-y.
Yeah, it smells Ume-y.
なんか... 薬臭くないちょっと。
Wait, doesn't it smell a bit like medicine?
じゃ、不健康の二人で。
Then, for the two unhealthy ones.
Sabotaged!
Cheers!
That sounds wonderful!
酸っめぇ！
So sour!
That's actually really good.
Really?
Wow.
Are you good?
酸っぱ...
Sour...
I think you're having a great time.
Well, it tastes better after a bit more time.
My face is turning into that lemon meme!
You know that lemon face just implodes?
薬っぽい味した。
It tasted like medicine.
I feel so healthy. Probably healthy.
That's it, guys! That's it! Whoo!
Okay, so we're going to return to the live performance...
and the second half includes new songs, so let's keep it going, guys!
Whoo! Yeah! Let's go!
All right, you guys are fine. Okay, let's get a move on.
Just, just, just get a move on.
All right.
Whoo! Yeah!
You still... really? I'm fine now.
だいぶ良くなったよ。
I'm much better now.
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Lyrics, Music: Amala
DAIDAIDAIDAIDAIKIRAI
ゼンゼン満たされない
Never satisfied
反吐が出るくらいに
Sickening enough to vomit
うざったいわ
So annoying
何言ったって不埒で
Whatever you say is insolent
ヘラって期待した
I lost my mind and hoped
私がバカだった
I was a fool
Yes! 現代の安保理
Yes! Modern UNSC
美神それゆえに
Because I'm a goddess of beauty
アンチない正気に
Sanity without haters
アサイーカパシティ
Acai capacity
毎度狂い
Going crazy every time
定まるとこ人生ずっと地味
In the end, life is always plain
見苦しい
Unsightly
痛々しい
Painful
無視できないのがいっそ腹立たしい
Being unable to ignore you is even more irritating
忌々しい
Cursed
そろそろ飽きた時間残飯に
I'm getting bored, time for the leftovers
わかったわ
I get it
ライトな反対売買
Light short selling
煽る視線AI効率
Provoking gaze, AI efficiency
被爆し
Exposed
切り離せない関係飛ばしてしまいたいわ
I want to blow away this inseparable relationship
これは祝いいわゆるエトセトラ
This is a celebration, so to speak, et cetera
迷声の生命の生命に乗せてんだ
Riding on the life of the life of a stray voice
何も守らない怠惰が気づいたミニマリズム
Minimalism noticed by laziness that protects nothing
悪信号にずっと執着です
Always obsessed with bad signals
ダイダイあなたのこと私ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
I really, really, really, really, really hate you
oh my god な情けないもはやバイバイバイバイバイしたい
Oh my god, how pathetic, I want to say bye-bye already
脳内妄想即能ゆえに解解解解解は無し
Delusions in the brain, immediate brain, so there is no release
頂戴私のことあなたダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Please, you really, really, really, really, really hate me
深淵向かい合って一理なし
Facing the abyss, no logic
nothing 足しもしもしただればなればでも
Nothing added, even if it was just a what-if
ニコチンらしい
Seems like nicotine
愛ミスして近づいてつまづく
Mistake in love, approach and stumble
ボミソニーサンキュー羽目を外して
Vomi-Sony thank you, letting loose
後味初期化してくるわ
The aftertaste is being reset
よしよし子猫が振りまきバラバラいい子ね
There, there, the kitten scatters, what a good girl
だけどだけどその本性は善悪の区別もつかないの
But, but, your true nature can't even tell right from wrong
幻影の色彩通り魔最強に混ざれて
Mixed in with the phantom colors, the strongest street slasher
障害ダイダイダイキライあなたと全然食い違っちゃった
Obstacle, I hate you so much, we're completely at odds
人は鏡なんです実のところ依存は両縁で
People are mirrors, in fact, dependence is mutual
シャットダウンしてもつきまとう己の様子が不甲斐ない
Even if I shut down, my lingering appearance is pathetic
全部全部あんたのせいで反吐が出るくらいに
Everything is all your fault, sickening enough to vomit
...も合わないわ
...doesn't match either.
いっそのこと切り離した方が楽なのみんな
It's easier for everyone to just cut it off.
大体あなたのこと私ダイダイダイダイ大嫌い
Basically, I hate, hate, hate, hate you so much.
お前が情けないもはやバイバイバイバイバイしたい
You're pathetic, I want to say bye, bye, bye, bye, bye now.
脳内もよそ見も言われカイカイカイカイ会話な
My mind, looking away, being told things, the conversation is itch-itch-itch-itch-itchy.
どうだって私のことあなたダイダイダイダイ大嫌い
No matter what, you hate, hate, hate, hate me so much.
愛想尽き果て一に無し七に蜂の巣ぶち込めば
Running out of patience, no one for one, seven for the honeycomb to be stuffed in.
鳴らねばならぬでもニコチンは死
It must ring, but nicotine is death.
愛に満ちて自画付いて結末はボミスボミス
Filled with love, self-satisfied, the end is a blunder, a blunder.
天気雨教師後味一生嫌でいたくないわ
Sunshower, teacher, aftertaste, I don't want to be hated for a lifetime.
I'm not interested in matching.
I'm gonna express myself in this song.
H A L F
簡単な英語しか分かんない
I only understand simple English.
踊るの大好き
I love to dance.
健康第一
Health first.
憧れとコンプレックス大渋滞
A big traffic jam of admiration and complexes.
カーストでノリノリ
Riding high on the caste.
カーストは飽き飽き
Sick and tired of the caste.
がむしゃらでいたい いつもいつでも
I want to be reckless, always and forever.
恵まれてるかどうかを
Whether I'm blessed or not...
楽しんでいたい 泣きたくないから
I want to have fun, because I don't want to cry.
問い質す神様がいなくても
Even if there's no God to question.
もう格好つけていくしかないじゃん
Now there's nothing left but to act cool, right?
そのままこのまま降り注ぐ光ね
Just as it is, just like this, the light pours down.
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of myself as just a half.
このままそのまま突き進む光
Like this, just like that, the light pushes forward.
ビジュアルなんかじゃ止まんない
Can't be stopped by just visuals.
笑わせたいのに
I want to make you laugh, but...
上手に出来ない
I can't do it well.
誰かのせいにはしたくないよ
I don't want to blame anyone.
生まれてみたいから
Because I wanted to be born...
生まれてきただけ
I was just born.
新しい服と幸せ
New clothes and happiness.
そんなに僕は無いでしょう
I don't have that much of them, do I?
それでも今も誰かが打ち放つ
Yet even now, someone unleashes...
悲しみと怒りの
...sadness and anger.
H A L F
損をしたり
Losing out,
ちょっと辛い
feeling a bit down...
そんな日もあるけど
There are days like that.
茨の道で花が咲くなら
If a flower blooms on a path of thorns,
絶対見逃せない
I definitely can't miss it.
もう格好つけていくしかないじゃん
Now there's nothing left but to act cool, right?
そのままこのまま降り注ぐ光ね
Just as it is, just like this, the light pours down.
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of myself as just a half.
このままそのまま突き進む光
Like this, just like that, the light pushes forward.
Ha...
X.U.
Lyrics: Benjamin, mpi Music: 澤野弘之
Lyrics: Benjamin, mpi Music: Hiroyuki Sawano
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame we will split it away
Don't take all of the weight you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights, such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, they'll change somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my dawn, before you can be turned
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
it is our pain that makes us all human after all
Who will save me? If you don't show
our fragile precious world
Must protect it, respond to the call
Are they really deep inside your head?
Do they control you like a little marionette?
I'll cut the strings off you dead, come in with me
let me free the wings of your soul and make it fly
We've been waiting here just to make you whole again
No more hating see I have always been your friend
Those eyes, no light, such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, they'll change somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my dawn, the shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
it is our pain that makes us all human after all
Warmth of safety, if you don't show
our fragile precious world
Must protect it, respond to the call
If you want to fight with me
Then go ahead and fight with me
Cause all I want to do is help you, man
You will be the death of me
The power of our army has been cut with us all
And if we lose you too then we may never survive
Interlace, but you must first believe
Just one step at a time
and keep your head up, boy, and you'll be free
Yay!
Hah... Phew...
So, how was that so far?
That was good! How did you feel?
That was good. Do you guys like how it's been going so far and the songs?
Yeah!
We just had all of our duo songs.
And we also went through the variety part and everything, yeah.
How are you guys feeling?
It still hurts.
I don't know how I danced with this foot.
How are you guys? You're probably fine.
Oh, no, no, no. No, I'm not worried about you at all.
How about you?
My foot still hurts.
But it's okay!
Yay! Persevere!
There's a surprise at the end, but before that...
We have an announcement about merchandise.
Check this out!
hololive English -Promise- 2nd Anniversary Celebration
I love the key visual! Yay!
It's the hololive English -Promise- 2nd Anniversary Celebration merch.
We're releasing merchandise to commemorate our second anniversary.
Let's take turns introducing the merch, shall we?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Frame Art Board
So first up is a Frame Art Board of our wonderful key visual for the Promise 2nd Anniversary.
The frame part uses luxurious sparkling paper and the printed illustration turns this...
...into a high-quality piece of art. Oh my! You definitely don't want to miss the chance...
...to add it to your collection or room. And guess what?
You can even hang it on the wall!
Oh my god, on the wall! On the wall!
Next up are the Collection Cards for each of Promise.
Collection Card
These cards feature an attractive design with a foil-stamped on the front...
...and you can choose each card individually, so be sure to collect all of them!
Gotta collect 'em all! Wow!
Next, we also have Ring Necklaces! Yay!
Ring Necklace
This design includes cute references and motifs for each of us.
You can use it as either a ring or a necklace, so feel free to change it up...
...depending on the occasion!
Yay! Next!
Tumbler
And next, we have special porcelain tumblers with our designs on them.
It features our talent colors on top of a black base.
They are designed to have a unified look, and I bet it'll look so cool...
...if you use several of these tumblers together in like a drinking party or something!
Yay! Okay, last one!
And lastly, we have a 2-way tote bag.
2-WAY Tote Bag
It's a 2-way design that can be used as both a shoulder bag and a tote bag. Oh, that's actually really cool.
It's even designed to be used as a carry-on bag too. Perfect for traveling and convenience.
And to top it off, it has many pockets that will definitely be useful...
...for storing small items like other merch!
Pockets! Oh my god!
Yes! And that concludes the Promise 2nd Anniversary merch introduction!
Yay! Please get it!
よろしくお願いいたします！
Thank you for your support!
Yay! Please get it! よろしくお願いいたします！
Yay! Please get it! Thank you for your support!
And with that, we're finally at the very last part.
Sorry for keeping you guys waiting.
We mentioned that there would be a special surprise or announcement earlier.
Would you like to hear what it is?
Yes!
I wonder what it is.
But before we announce it...
...it's time for a stage change!
Stage change! Whoa! Oh my god! We're floating! We're going up! No!
Whoa!
Wait, stop, stop, stop!
Oh my god! No, IRyS is mine!
Okay, we're good, we're good, we're good. Okay.
I'm getting claustrophobic!
I'm gonna be sick!
Okay, it's open.
I see the light.
Oh my goodness.
Okay. Nice. That's nice.
I feel fresh air.
All righty. Well, ladies, it is time for our final announcement.
Final announcement?
We, Promise, have a new original song!
Finally releasing, it's called Run Back 'Round.
Run Back 'Round! Our first new song!
Look at that!
We worked really, really hard on this song,
and it's really cool, really catchy.
It's quite different to, you know, a lot of the original songs
that we as Promise have put out before.
Yeah! We hope that you guys will listen to it a lot.
The chorus part is quite hype and honestly quite easy to remember,
so I feel like, you know, hopefully it becomes an earworm
and you can go put it on loop over and over and over again.
That's our big reveal.
Hope you're excited!
I'm so excited! Yay!
Well, I think all that's left is for us to perform our new song.
What? We're gonna perform it here? Right here?
Floating here in the city. Yeah! Floating here.
But before we go, do you have any final thoughts about our live, about our anniversary?
I am just super happy we got to do this as Promise,
and you know, it was a lot of fun singing all these songs with you guys,
you know, different duets, and I just really like the fact that we have a hideout now.
We do! We finally have our hideout now!
We have a bar too! For celebration!
Catch you at the bar. Yeah.
And it's in a fabulous location.
Imagine how expensive the rent is. Yeah.
Don't let them pay for it. We'll all pay for it. All good.
So, yeah, I'm really happy. How about you guys?
Yeah, I'm just really thankful that, you know, we're still here after two years,
and you know, hope everyone continues to support Promise. Thank you guys.
And here's to many, many more! Yay!
I could say the same thing. I'm just gonna steal everyone's and say that it's been great being with all of you for two years,
and you know, now we get to have this cool hideout,
and this awesome song that we get to show everyone. So, yay!
We ready?
Yes.
I'm ready.
Let's go!
Ready, set, go!
Run Back 'Round!
Run back 'round...
Don't stop now...
Up with the moonlight,
Down in the streetlights,
Looking for a spotlight,
Making my move
Whoa
I'm running
行こう (Ikou)
Let's go
Days like a whirlwind,
don't stop coming,
Got me in a tailspin,
What can I do?
Whoa
Keep running!
行こう (Ikou)
Let's go
Lost and found,
back to where I started,
I won't stay down,
trust me, I can do it!
I live life loud,
take it to the limit,
So stand up proud,
now I'm gonna sing it!
Run back 'round,
it's a new beginning,
I run back 'round,
got to keep believing,
I know where I'm going,
I run back 'round,
nothing's gonna stop me now!
Woah oh oh!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Sparks on the pavement,
dreams in the distance,
Gotta be relentless,
faster than sound
Whoa
Keep running!
行こう (Ikou)
Let's go
Oh yeah...
Lock it and load it, 僕らは explosive
Lock it and load it, we are explosive
Swifter and lighter, 明日ももっと brighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow will be even brighter
Oh yeah...
Faster than lightning, about to get exciting
Keep on running...
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning
I run back 'round, got to keep believing
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going
Day and night I'm running, I run back 'round
Nothing's gonna stop me now!
Hoo... Woah, oh, oh!
止められないよ!
Can't stop now!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!
走って 走って 走って
Run, run, run
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!
始まるよ
It's beginning
I'm coming around, I've got a dream just waiting now
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!
Yeah, everybody, come on!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!